-= 飘域家园 =-
bbs.homefei.net
3D大片 BT高清影视 游戏 软件 音乐 电子书
在战争中，第一个倒下的是真理
- 埃斯库罗斯
肯尼亚，内罗比，伊斯特利
东非时间，早上 7:00
天眼行动
英格兰，萨里
格林威治标准时间，凌晨 4:15
索马里
他们射杀了安瓦尔
爆炸新闻：青年党处死了告密嫌疑人
祝今天好运
弗兰克
国防部副部长，弗兰克·贝森中将
美国，内华达州，拉斯维加斯
太平洋标准时间，晚上 8:45
常设联合总部
伦敦，诺斯伍德
乔莫·肯雅塔机场
肯尼亚，内罗比
克里奇空军基地
美国，内华达州
英国内阁府
伦敦，白厅
我们找到她了！
我们应该袭击
我们找到她了！我们应该袭击
注意，内阁府不同意消灭她
需要一个抓捕选择
在他们离开那之前，没可能
正在计算
高度匹配
检查其他几个房间
他们正在上报
他们正在武装，我需要回答，马上
中国北京
你已获得许可
能买下那些饼吗
还有车子？
别管它
无信号
-= 飘域家园 =-
bbs.homefei.net
3D大片 BT高清影视 游戏 软件 音乐 电子书
导演 加文·胡德
主演 海伦·米伦
主演 亚伦·保尔
主演 艾伦·里克曼
天眼行动
这是我有过的最漂亮的了
是啊，宝贝，做好了
玩去吧
看呐，妈妈
棒极了，阿丽亚
爸爸，数学好难哦
继续努力
好吧，爸爸
有客人
把书都给我
我就来
你好
我自行车坏了
能帮我修好吗？
行，没问题
我一会儿回来拿
如果可以的话
阿丽亚，面包烤好了
好
嘿，你的手腕怎么没被盖上？
- 快走，快走  - 好，好，行了
- 快走  - 好
面包多少钱？
五十先令
太贵了
四十五卖吗？
好吧
好
谢谢
- 这个多少钱？ - 八十一个
我全要了，两千
两千？两千？
对
拿去，拿去
- 这个呢？  - 什么？
四百卖吗？
四百买我的夹克？
四百不行，给我一千
我就把夹克给你
好，脱下来吧
给我吧
不会再有偷窃了
感谢主，的确如此
现在，你可以敞开门睡觉了
你说的对
这是你的钱
祝福你
有问题随时回来找我
谢谢
这姑娘在做什么？
你在干嘛？
对不起，爸爸
没有下次了
好的，爸爸
真抱歉
没事
她还是个孩子
你说的对
你在想什么呢？
爸爸，对不起
听我说
那些人都是盲信徒
不要在他们面前玩
是，爸爸
永远不要
好的，爸爸
但是我可以在你面前玩，对吗？
对，宝贝，当然可以
玩去吧
嘿，你，站住
把这下放下，放下
- 把桶子分开  - 它们只是桶子
里面装了什么？
好吧
里面什么也没有，我就是个做买卖的
只是几个桶子而已
- 走  - 我可以走了吗？
走
那是电子游戏吗？
对啊
是什么游戏啊？
不适合你们小孩子玩
我可以跟你一起玩吗？
你叫什么名字？
哈立德
想要份工作吗？
想
把那些桶卖了，一半的钱我都给你
这些桶？
对
朋友，你真是个好人
这些吗？
对，别再多问了
桶子，桶子
赚了一百四十先令
你真厉害
如果我再卖一个，可以让我玩游戏吗？
不，不，继续卖
桶子，桶子，桶子
哈立德，我很快就要走，你现在可以走了
给我一小时让我把这些都卖出去
留三个给我，剩下的都拿走
这些？
对
你确定吗
对，回家去
别去其他任何地方
明白吗
好
给你
去吧
多少钱？
五十
我全要了
全部？
对
你确定吗
嘿，你
回家去
我认识你
我以前住在这，朋友
我现在是商人了，卖桶
你到哪去了？
我回了趟索马里，我妈妈病了
不不，我想起来了
这个人，我以前把他赶出去过
他爱个肯尼亚人
来，抓住他
- 你好，阿丽亚  - 你好
- 你好吗  - 我很好
你妈妈呢
我要一个
五十先令
走，走
两个是一百吗
是的
好
小伙子，过来
你叫什么
阿里
阿里，你帮我个忙，我就给你点钱
拿上所有这些钱给我买点面饼
绕过清真寺左转
在角落有个女孩卖饼
买下她所有的饼，剩下的钱你留着
如果你五分钟内回来…
什么
我会把所有这些钱都给你
是，先生
快跑去吧
面饼？
不要
- 谢谢  - 谢谢
- 干得好，阿里，干得好  - 我买到面饼了，买到了
谢谢你
救命啊
帮帮我
帮帮我，求你了
求你了，帮帮我
帮我一下
救命，医生在哪？
抱歉，罗科
Sorry, Rocco.
来，来
Come, come.
乖狗狗
Good dog.
青年党处死了告密嫌疑人
索马里青年党激进分子
Somali Al-Shabab militants
张贴出了这张姓名未知男子的照片
have posted this picture of an unnamed man
他们说他们已经在内罗比将其处死
they say they have executed in Nairobi.
他们声称他是个间谍
They claim he was a spy
是英国和肯尼亚情报局的走狗
working for British and Kenyan intelligence services,
企图破坏他们招募和运送
attempting to disrupt the recruiting and trafficking
年轻的西部穆斯林成员们
of young Western Muslims.
肯尼亚境内的青年党极端主义
Al-Shabab extremism within Kenya
在两年前的西门购物商场袭击事件中
escalated with the Westgate shopping mall attack
已经升级
in Nairobi two years ago,
那场事件导致了六十七人死亡，一百七十五人受伤
in which 67 people died and 175 were injured.
四月，该组织在加里萨大学大肆屠杀了
In April, the group massacred 147 students and staff
一百四十七名学生和教职工
at Garissa University College.
青年党想将他们严格的
Al-Shabab want to impose their strict version
伊斯兰教教法强加于整个非洲之角
of Sharia law across the Horn of Africa.
他们对英国和肯尼亚军方所扮演的
They bitterly resent the role of Britain and the Kenyan military
由英国支持的索马里政府叫苦不迭
in propping up the UN-backed Somali government.
- 早啊，上校  - 早，泰德
Morning, Colonel. Morning, Ted.
早上好
Good morning.
- 早上好，长官  - 早上好，上校
Good morning, ma'am. Morning, Colonel.
关于白鹭计划的三号视角已经就绪
Version three on Operation Egret is ready.
艾哈迈德家的数据就在三号幻灯片里
Ahmed's house data is on slide three.
谢谢
Thank you.
反坦克导弹
只有两枚“狱火”吗？我的那些GBU-12呢？
Only two Hellfires? Where are my GBU-12s?
长官，根据任务简报，我们认为应该
Well, ma'am, given the mission brief, we thought we should
减少毛重和递增的闲荡时间
decrease the gross weight and increase the loiter time.
所以我就只有“狱火”？
So I've only got the Hellfires?
是的，长官
Yes, ma'am.
赛德，你下次再改变装载
Sadd, next time you change the load out,
请先跟我确认清楚，好吗？
you check with me first, please?
- 是，长官  - 谢谢
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
路上还顺利吗？
How was your flight?
早上好，上将
General, good morning.
你收到我邮件了吗？
You got my email?
是的，长官，非常令人心寒
Yes, sir. Very upsetting.
他的家人会需要我们的扶持
His family will need our support.
交给我吧
Leave it with me.
- 一切都就绪了吗？  - 是的，长官
Everything in place? Yes, sir.
我一小时后就将到内阁府
I'll be at Cobra in an hour.
没问题
That should be fine.
祝你今天好运，凯瑟琳
Good luck today, Katherine.
谢谢
Thank you.
这里是七号训令室吗？
Is this Briefing Room 7?
对，没事，我们还没开始
Yeah. You're fine. We haven't started yet.
我是瓦特斯中尉
Lieutenant Watts.
飞行员格申
Airman Gershon.
幸会
Pleasure.
准备
Stand by.
全体人员注意
Room, attention.
继续
Carry on.
好，我一会儿把你们介绍给伦敦的鲍威尔上校
All right, I'm going to introduce you guys to Colonel Powell in London.
- 少校，帮我们接通  - 是，长官
- Push us through please, Major. - Yes, sir.
早上好，上校，能听清楚吗？
Good morning, Colonel. Are we coming through clear?
非常清楚，谢谢你，上校
Loud and clear, Colonel, thank you.
很高兴又见面了
Good to see you again.
我也是，我已经将你的组员准备好了
And you, ma'am. I have your crew ready.
请做自我介绍吧
Introduce yourselves, please.
早上好，长官，我是飞行员 机长，史蒂夫·瓦特斯中尉
Morning, ma'am. Lieutenant Steve Watts, Aircraft Commander, Pilot.
空军一等兵，卡莉·格申，传感器操作员
Airman First Class Carrie Gershon, Sensor Operator.
空军下士，马特·勒夫瑞，任务协调员
Senior Airman Matt Levery, Mission Intel Coordinator.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天，你们将操作一架无人机飞往肯尼亚，内罗比
Today, you will be flying a joint operation over Nairobi, Kenya,
代号为白鹭行动
codename Operation Egret.
非洲角，索马里，肯尼亚，内罗比
Horn of Africa, Somalia, Kenya, Nairobi.
我们得到情报，青年党将在帕克兰郊区的
We have intelligence of a meeting of key members of Al-Shabab
这栋房子里召开主要成员会议
in the suburb of Parklands in this house, here.
屋主名叫舍希德·艾哈迈德
It belongs to a man named Shahid Ahmed.
他是一个青年党促进者
He's an Al-Shabab facilitator.
拜访这里的是这个人
Due to visit this house is this man,
阿布杜拉·艾哈迪
Abdullah Al-Hady.
他是个索马里人，他的妻子爱莎·艾哈迪
He's a Somali, and his wife, Ayesha Al-Hady,
原名苏珊·海伦·丹福特，国籍是英国
formerly Susan Helen Danford, British national.
童年时期就各种惹是生非，十五岁时改变信仰
Troubled childhood, converted at 15.
她是在西伦敦区的一座清真寺里被激进化的
She was radicalized in a West London mosque
她在那里遇见了艾哈迪，并嫁给了他
where she met and married Al-Hady.
情报显示，他们与肯尼亚
Intelligence has them connected
近期发生的自杀性爆炸事件有关
to the most recent suicide bombing in Kenya.
他们是我们东非通缉要犯名单上的第四，第五名
They are numbers four and five on our East Africa Most Wanted list.
我们已经追踪他们六年了
We've been tracking them for six years.
他们昨天处死了我们的一个肯尼亚特工
Their cell executed one of our Kenyan agents yesterday.
现在我们得到消息，他们今天将会到内罗比
Now we have information that they will be in Nairobi today,
使用帕克兰的房子，作为两批新成员的转接点
using that Parklands house as a transit point for two new recruits.
穆罕默德·艾迪萨拉姆，美国人
Muhammad Abdisalaam, American.
中情局将他与明尼苏达的激进分子相关联
The CIA have him connected to extremists in Minnesota.
还有拉希德·哈姆德，他是个英国人
And Rasheed Hamud. He's British.
等这些嫌犯一旦进入屋子
Once all suspects are in the house,
肯尼亚特种部队将会拉出警戒线，并进行搜查
Kenyan special forces will launch a cordon and search.
这是抓捕计划，不是杀戮
This is an operation to capture, not kill.
你们的工作，就是成为他们的天眼
Your job is to be their eye in the sky.
明白，谢谢，女士，挂断吧
Right, thank you, ma'am. Kill it.
- 是，长官  - 去做准备吧
Yes, sir. Go brief.
长官，您来这多久了？
So, sir, how long have you been here?
大概六个月，你呢？
About six months now. You?
我刚来
Just got here.
哇，那你喜欢维加斯吗？
Oh, wow. How are you liking Vegas?
感觉挺刺激的
It can get a little wild.
那还用说
That it can.
你家乡是哪的啊？
Where are you from originally?
- 我来自俄亥俄州  - 俄亥俄？
I'm from Ohio. Ohio?
那，那你来自哪？
Where are you... Where are you from?
爱达荷，你什么时候取得资格的？
Idaho. When did you qualify?
一个月前
A month ago.
哇，对我来说，也不过是两年前的事啊
Wow. It's only been about two years for me.
你为什么加入这？
Why'd you join?
为了偿还巨额的大学贷款
I'd racked up a lot of college debt.
空军保证我有四年的工作
Air Force was a guaranteed four years of work.
- 嘿，伙计们  - 嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hi.
- 嘿  - 嘿
Hey. Hey.
你们有看见长颈鹿吗？
You seen any giraffes?
是的，看见了
Matter of fact, yeah.
是啊，一大群呢
Oh, wow. Yeah, a whole bunch of them
大概在城市以东三十英里
about 30 miles east of the city.
飞机刚在轨道里安顿下来了
The aircraft is established in the orbit
飞行高度为两百，十分隐秘
at Flight Level 200, running covert.
GCS：门控开关
飞机和GCS一切正常，没有任何写入
Aircraft and GCS are in the green with no write-ups.
好，很好
Okay. Great.
所有的镜头都完好无损
All cameras checked good.
这是目标
Here's the target.
地面部队就在几个街区远的一个旧工厂里
Ground forces are a few blocks away in an old factory.
这里
Over here.
好的，谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
武器加快自旋都正常
Weapons all spun up good.
空中待命还剩十小时
Ten hours' time on station remaining.
你们还有两枚“狱火”导弹，安全无线电也完好无损
You still have two Hellfire missiles. Secure radio checked good.
很好，谢谢各位
Great. Thank you, guys.
好了，好好干，别搞砸了
All right. Do good. Don't suck.
嘿，马特？你进来了吗？
Hey, Matt? You strapped in?
我在呢，这就来
I'm here. Here it comes.
肖曼5-0，北部2-0，早上好，莫斯，你好吗？
Showman 5-0, North 2-0. Good morning, Moses. How are you?
北部2-0，肖曼5-0，早上好，上校，我很好，谢谢
North 2-0, Showman 5-0. Good morning, Colonel. Very good, thank you.
确保海鹰在蓝色区域
Confirm Seahawk is in the Blue Zone,
但是秃鹰还在飞行中，对吗？
but Condor is still in flight, right?
海鹰在蓝色区域
Seahawk is in the Blue Zone.
我们希望秃鹰一小时后能着陆
We expect Condor to land in an hour.
谢谢，你们都就位了吗？
Thank you. Are your men in place?
是的，长官
Yes, ma'am.
宝贝，我是爸爸
Darling, it's your dad here.
我现在正看着一橱柜的安娜贝尔洋娃娃
I'm looking at a whole shelf of these Annabell dolls.
你没跟我说它们有这么多款式啊
You didn't tell me that there were different types.
我不知道该买哪一个
I have no idea what to buy her.
你能尽快回复我吗？
Can you get back to me ASAP?
不然…
Otherwise...
呃…
Um...
我现在正拿着一个“该睡觉了”娃娃
I'm holding a "Time to Sleep" doll.
上面写着，“当到了晚安时刻
It says here, "You will hear her babbling"
你会听见她的咿呀声”
"when it is beddy-byes."
尽快给我回电
Call me as soon as you can.
我是本森上将，来开内阁府会议
General Benson here for Cobra.
本森上将
General Benson.
杰克·克里利，我是今天的协调员
Jack Cleary. I'm coordinating today.
- 先生，这边请  - 谢谢
This way, sir. Thank you.
等等，“动感宝宝”？我买的是什么？
Hold on a minute. "Baby Moves"? What have I got?
好吧，有关系吗？我是说…
Well, does it matter? I mean...
上将，他们在找您了，先生
General, they're asking for you, sir.
对，好的，亲爱的，我试试看
Yes. Uh... All right, darling, I'll try.
好吧，拜拜
Yup. Bye-bye.
我本该买一个“动感宝宝”
I bought a "Time to Sleep" doll
结果我买了一个“该睡觉了”娃娃
when I should have bought a "Baby Moves."
显然，他们之间的区别很大
Apparently, there's an important difference.
长官，交给我来办吧
I'll see what I can do, sir.
内阁府训令室“A”
- 早上好，司法部长  - 早上好，弗兰克
Attorney General, good morning. Good morning, Frank.
- 首相  - 上将
Minister. General.
女士
Ma'am.
祝贺你任新职了
Congratulations on your new appointment.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想和你们谈谈苏珊·丹福特的抓捕行动
I'm gonna talk you through the capture of Susan Danford,
也就是爱莎·艾哈迪
AKA Ayesha Al-Hady.
- 你好吗？  - 我很好，你呢？
How are you? I'm good, and you?
欢迎来到内罗比
Welcome to Nairobi.
秃鹰已降落
The Condor has landed.
收到，到蓝色区域去
Copy that. Proceed to the Blue Zone.
- 嘿  - 嘿
Hey. Hey.
- 你去看比赛了吗？ - 我太忙了
Did you go to the game? I was busy.
图像分析部，珍珠港
你也许还能赶上
You might still make it.
我们拍到什么了？
What have we got here?
正在追踪内罗比的某个激进分子
Tracking some extremists in Nairobi.
我的一个同乡
One guy's from my hometown.
开玩笑，说真的？
You're kidding. Serious?
- 对  - 这个是他吗？
Yup. Uh-huh. Is that him?
穆罕默德·艾迪萨拉姆，索马里人
Muhammad Abdisalaam, Somali.
那边有很多他们这种人
A lot of them there.
好吧，那但愿他回不来
Well, let's hope he's not coming back.
- 是啊，值班顺利  - 谢谢
Yeah. Have a good shift. Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you. Mmm-hmm.
情况怎么样了？
What's going on?
秃鹰正在蓝色区域
We've got Condor in the Blue Zone.
秃鹰是谁啊？
Who the fuck is Condor?
就是机场的第二个人
The second guy in from the airport.
我记不住这么多名字
I can't keep up with these names.
肖曼5-0，能看到屋内的画面吗？
Showman 5-0, can we get a view into the house?
佩格9-0, 肖曼5-0，能试试调取屋内的画面吗？
Peg 9-0, Showman 5-0, can you try and look into the house?
正在调取
Moving now.
肖曼5-0，要我们派林戈去吗？
Showman 50, would you like us to bring in Ringo?
不用，等候三号抵达
Negative. Wait for number three to arrive.
有动静了
We have movement.
见鬼，他们这是要走了吗？
Damn it. Are they leaving?
丹福特和艾哈迪呢？
Where are Danford and Al-Hady?
上校，根据我们的情报，他们半小时后会到
Colonel, our intelligence only has them arriving in another half hour.
好吧，那我们的情报都太不灵通了
Well, then our intelligence is bad.
装载！
Load up!
北部2-0，肖曼5-0，我的人已经准备好了，进去吗？
North 2-0, Showman 5-0, I have my men ready. Do we go in?
不，不，不，少校，让你的人等等，我要抓丹福特
No, no, no. No, Major, please. Hold your men. I want Danford.
收到，立定！稍息！
Copy. Halt! Hold up!
立定！
Halt!
亡命徒2-7，如果他们离开，就继续跟踪
Bravo 2-7, follow if they leave.
夏威夷五号，做人脸识别
Hawaii 5, confirm PID.
收到，北部2-0，请再靠近点
Roger, North 2-0. I'd like to be closer.
佩格9-0，靠近点，去做人脸识别
Peg 9-0, go closer for PID.
北部2-0，夏威夷五号，人脸识别已确认对象为…
North 2-0, Hawaii 5 confirms positive IDs on
穆罕默德·艾迪萨拉姆和拉希德·哈姆德
Muhammad Abdisalaam and Rasheed Hamud.
收到
Roger that.
- 那是谁？  - 放大
Who's that? Zoom in.
那个是丹福特吗？
Is that Danford?
做个人脸识别
I need a PID.
该死
Shit.
见鬼，那是她吗？还是艾哈迈德的老婆？
Damn it. Is that her, or does Ahmed have a wife?
抱歉，上校，我们不清楚
I'm sorry, Colonel, we don't know.
不，这样还不够出色，各位
No, not good enough, people.
那肯定是她
It has to be her.
为什么我们不知道她已经在那屋子里了？
Why didn't we know she was already in the house?
行动者，说出意图
Movers, say intentions.
- 继续停留在PAX  - 明白
- Stay on PAX. - Copy.
亡命徒2-7正在跟踪
Bravo 2-7 following.
夏威夷五号，得到画面后，我要你尽快做人脸识别
Hawaii 5, I want a PID on that woman as soon as we get a visual.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
缩小
Zoom out.
北部2-0，肖曼5-0
North 2-0. Showman 5-0.
他们好像是要去伊斯特利
Looks like they're heading towards Eastleigh.
她要是进那去了，我们还怎么发起地面攻击？
So, how do we launch a ground assault if she's going in there?
没办法，青年党控制了那片区域
We can't. Al-Shabab controls that neighborhood.
那会触发大屠杀
It would trigger a massacre.
好吧，好吧，那…
All right. All right, just...
就跟着她
Just stay with her.
肖曼5-0，亡命徒2-7
Showman 50, Bravo 27.
继续跟下去太冒险了
It's too risky to follow.
回基地
Return to base.
肖曼5-0，这房子我们认识吗？
Showman 5-0, do we know this house?
那是阿玛度·穆赫塔尔的家
It belongs to Amadu Mukhtar.
他是个索马里商人，除此之外，没有其他数据
He's a Somali trader, but there is no other intel on him.
该死
Oh, shit.
夏威夷五号，北部2-0，你有看见点什么吗？
Hawaii 5, North 2-0. Did you see anything there?
- 没有，长官  - 见鬼
No, ma'am. Shit.
肖曼5-0，我们需要在屋内安插一个眼
Showman 5-0, we need an eye inside that house.
我必须知道丹福特是否在里面，以及谁和她在一起
I have to know if Danford is inside, and who is with her.
长官，那意味着要安排一个人在街上
Ma'am, it would mean putting a man in the street,
而且要靠近到能够控制甲壳虫
and you'd have to get close to control the beetle.
那样很容易引起怀疑
It would easily raise suspicion.
怎么，就连用个索马里人也会引起怀疑？
What, even if you use a Somali?
任何陌生人都有嫌疑，就算是索马里人
Every stranger is suspicious, even a Somali.
莫斯，我们都确信那个丹福特就在屋里，对吗？
Moses, we both believe that Danford is inside that house, do we not?
是的，长官
Yes, ma'am.
而没有人脸识别，我就不能授权发起袭击
And I cannot authorize a strike without a positive ID.
我觉得我们必须接受风险，派个人进去
I believe we have to accept the risk and send someone in.
莫斯，你能做到吗？
Moses, can you do it?
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
谢谢，非常感谢
Thank you. Appreciate what you're doing.
佩格9-0，肖曼5-0
Peg 9-0, Showman 5-0.
我需要你设法让林戈进入目标房屋内
I need you to engage Ringo at the target house.
我们需要进行人脸识别
We need a positive ID.
好了
Okay.
谢谢你，伙计
Thanks, man. Mmm-hmm.
什么鬼？
What?
阿丽亚
Alia.
那是什么？
What's that?
让林戈绕到另一边去识别那个女人
Get Ringo around the other side to identify the woman.
那就是丹福特，夏威夷五号，请进行人脸识别
That's Danford. Hawaii 5, confirm PID, please.
识别，苏珊·海伦·丹福特
PID, Susan Helen Danford.
我们找到丹福特了
We have Danford.
但是我们无法进入民兵监管区
But we can't enter the militia-controlled area.
不
No.
上将，你有什么计划？
What's the plan, General?
那个，使用“收割者”，我们有能力
Well, using the Reaper, we have the ability
用一个相当的精准度 袭击一个目标
to strike a target with considerable accuracy.
首相，只要你同意
If you agree, Minister,
我们可以消灭她
we could eliminate her.
绝对不行！
Absolutely not!
女士，她是一个青年党成员
Ma'am, she's a member of Al-Shabab
而且是东非要犯通缉名单上的第四位
and number four on our East African Most Wanted list.
上将，我不在乎你的名单
I don't care about your list, General.
我来这是为了目睹一次抓捕行动
I came here to witness a capture,
而不是消灭一个目标
not a targeted assassination.
乔治
George.
是的，很抱歉，弗兰克，我同意安吉拉的看法
Yes, I'm sorry, Frank. I agree with Angela.
我们的本意是抓捕丹福特，而不是杀了她
The idea was to capture Danford, not kill her.
这项任务是由首相认可的
This was the mission approved by the PM.
而且，和司法部长一样，抓捕才是我来这想看到的
And, as Attorney General, that is what I came here to witness.
我们希望把她带回这个国家受审
We want her brought back to this country to stand trial.
对
Right.
我转告一下鲍威尔上校
I'll put that to Colonel Powell.
怎么样了？
What's happening?
不知道
I don't know.
嘿，马特，情况怎么样了？
Hey, Matt, what's going on?
我们弄了只甲壳虫进屋
We got a beetle inside that house,
看到了一群我们不太喜欢的人
and we're seeing a bunch of people we don't like.
那个是他，是她丈夫，夏威夷5号，进行确认
That's him. That's her husband. Hawaii 5, confirm.
肖曼5-0，他们俩我们都找到了
Showman 5-0, we've got them both.
是的，长官，真是太好了
Yes, ma'am. This is wonderful.
我需要佩格9-0带我去另几个房间
I need Peg 9-0 to take me into the other rooms.
该死
Shit.
操，天呐
Oh, fuck, man.
- 我操，我操  - 马特，怎么了？
Fuck. Fuck. Matt, what's happening?
我们在那个屋子里看见了一堆
We're seeing suicide vests and a whole bunch of fucking explosives
自杀性爆炸背心
inside that house.
好吧，这情况就不同了
Well, this changes things.
好吧，保持冷静，好吗？别让我的飞行员紧张
All right. Keep it calm, okay? Don't wind up my pilot.
立刻派律师过来
I want legal in here right now.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
他们要录制自杀录像
They're gonna make a suicide video.
上校，那是谁？
Who is that, Colonel?
好像是奥斯曼·阿比德
Looks like Osman Abade.
拉姆爆炸事件中的爆炸物就是他提供的
He supplied the explosives in the Lamu bombing.
凯瑟琳，计划是什么？
What's the plan, Katherine?
我们要立即往那个屋顶投一枚“狱火”
We need to put a Hellfire through that roof right now.
我说过了，他们是来目击抓捕行动，不是杀戮
I told you, they came to witness a capture, not a kill.
给我一个抓捕选择
Give me a capture option.
我们已经没有抓捕选择了
We no longer have a capture option.
任何地面行动都会导致一场武装对抗
Any action on the ground will lead to an armed confrontation,
那将是我们无法牵制的
which we will not be able to contain.
他们正在看着
They're watching.
就算出现了背心，我们也需要他们的许可才能袭击
Even with the vests, we need their approval for a strike.
就告诉他们，我们发现了丹福特
Just tell them we've got Danford in our sights.
我是说，光这一点，就该使用狱火了
I mean, that alone should justify using a Hellfire.
那些背心只是附加条件
The vests are just a bonus.
丹福特是英国公民，他们希望她活着
Danford's a British citizen. They want her alive.
他们不能让她活着！
They cannot have her alive!
弗兰克，我已经追踪她六年了
Frank, I've tracked her for six years.
这是我最接近她的一次
This is the closest I've ever got.
所以，我们现在就需要扩大规则
So, we need to expand our rules of engagement right now
以保护平均人口
to protect the civilian population.
往那屋顶上投放“狱火”就是我们
A Hellfire through that roof is our
最实际的选择
most effective option.
我们必须弄清楚，我们是合法的
We have to know that we're legally in the clear.
对，对，当然，我现在正在处理这个问题
Yes. Yes, of course. I'm getting into that right now.
上校？
Colonel?
- 哈罗德，情况你都清楚了吗？  - 是的，长官
Oh, Harold, you've been following? Yes, ma'am.
计划是往那屋顶上
So, the plan is to put a Hellfire
投一枚“狱火”
through the roof of that house.
我现在需要法律建议
I need legal clearance right now.
- 从“收割者”上发射一枚导弹？  - 是的
A missile from the Reaper? Yes.
这么说这已经不是抓捕行动了
So, this is no longer a capture situation.
对，我们在屋里发现了，两套自杀性爆炸背心
No. We have two suicide vests with explosives inside that house.
附加损害
你能为我通过更高的CDE吗？
So, can you clear me to a higher CDE?
这…
Uh...
哈罗德，这是一个非常时效性的目标，我有权进行袭击吗？
Harold, this is a very time-sensitive target. Do I have authority to strike?
你所遵循的交战规则
The rules of engagement you're operating under
只允许一个低量的附带损害
only allow for a low collateral damage estimate.
对，对，而我的武器只恳求一个低CDE
Yes, yes, and my weapons only invoke a low CDE.
是那屋子里的爆炸物
It's the explosives inside that house
带来了潜在的高CDE
that bring it to a potentially high CDE.
既然你知道里面有爆炸物
And since you know the explosives are there,
那把这点纳入考虑，则是义不容辞的
it is incumbent upon you to take them into account.
我能预见一个潜在的合法反对
I can see a potential legal objection.
老天，我们在那屋内发现了
Jesus! We've got two suicide bombers
两套自杀性炸弹，还有三个非常关键的人物！
and three very high value individuals inside that house!
我明白你希望将他们从你的名单上抹除
And you want them off your list, I understand that.
但你所遵循的交战规则
But the rules of engagement you're operating under
预设是一次抓捕行动，而不是杀戮方案
envisaged a capture, not a kill scenario.
长官，我觉得上报会更为明智
Ma'am, I think it would be wise to refer up.
你是在建议我，还是在反驳我？
Are you telling me that, or just debating with me?
关于上报？
To refer up?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
我是在建议你
I am telling you. Oh!
- 本森  - 长官
- Benson. - Sir.
律师建议我上报司法部长
Legal has advised me to refer up to the Attorney General.
弗兰克，我需要一个快速的回答
I need a quick answer, Frank.
好，我让他来接电话
Okay, I'll put that to him.
乔治
George.
这些爆炸物意味着紧迫的威胁
Those explosives mean there is an imminent threat
会对平均人口造成严重伤害
of serious harm to the civilian population.
我们能袭击吗？
Can we strike?
那个，考虑到新出现的情况，我会说，同意
Well, given the new circumstances, I would say yes.
布莱恩
Brian.
我们必须先打一通政治电话和法律电话
There is a political as well as a legal call to be made here.
是的，乔治，我意识到了
Yes, I'm quite aware of that, George.
首相，我们现在就需要一个决定
We need a decision now, Minister.
法律上，我们没有问题吗？
Legally, we don't have a problem?
是的，没有
No, we don't.
但政治上…
But politically...
是否允许我们进行？
Do we have permission to proceed?
那个
Well,
- 乔治，你似乎在暗示“是”  - 谢谢
you seem to be implying yes, George. Thank you.
- 稍等，等一下  - 不，我不是那意思…
Hold on a minute. Hold on. No. That is not what I...
这是抓捕任务转变为了击杀任务，对吗？
This is a change of mission from a capture to a shoot-to-kill, isn't it?
是的，没错
Yes, it is.
我们这么做没问题吗？
Are we all right with that?
我确定这样是有问题的
I'm sure we are not.
目标是两名英国公民和一个美国公民
There are two British citizens and an American as targets.
此次任务已经得到了
This mission has the full support
肯尼亚和美国的全力支持
of Kenya and the United States.
无人机袭击？
For a drone strike?
对，“收割者”上的导弹
Yes, a missile fired from an RPA
就是作为出现这种情况的
is part of an agreed contingency plan
应急计划的一部分
in circumstances like this.
我们能够进行攻击？
Do we have permission to proceed?
不，这种计划在没有得到国会的授权前
No. Such a plan should not have been signed off by the PM
首相是不能授权的
without the authority of Parliament.
战略操作本来通常就不在内阁进行讨论
Operational issues are not generally discussed at Cabinet,
毫无疑问，也不会在国会讨论
and certainly not at Parliament.
我很清楚草案，我说的是应该怎么做
I know the protocol. I'm talking about what should be happening.
安吉拉，在我看来，对于一次袭击来说
Angela, in my view, all the legal criteria
它已经符合了所有法律要件
for an attack have been met.
也就是说，这是军事需要
Namely, this is a military necessity,
没有其他合理的选择
there is no reasonable alternative,
而且我们被迫消除威胁
and the force to be used is in proportion to the threat.
这么说，应该解决了你的疑问
That should answer your question.
并没有，乔治
It does not, George.
历史上曾经有过一艘由英国驾驶的无人机袭击一个
Has there ever been a British-led drone attack on a city
未在交战中的友国的城市？
in a friendly country that is not at war?
上将？
General?
我想没有，是的
I do not believe so, no.
那我们怎么能认可它？
Then how can we sanction it?
重新生成这些无人机上的导弹
Generate new damage rings for the compound
所形成的破坏圈
with an assessment of the payload on those jackets.
- 是，长官  - 立刻
Yes, ma'am. Right now.
- 沃什上校  - 上校
- Colonel Walsh. - Colonel.
我能直接和你的飞行员通话吗？
Can I speak to your pilot directly?
是的，长官，帮我接线
Yes, ma'am. Patch me through.
史蒂夫
Steve.
鲍威尔上校想和你直接谈谈，接吧
Colonel Powell wants to talk to you directly. Pick up.
长官
Ma'am.
中尉
Lieutenant.
你现在是我们消灭这些难题的最佳选择
You are now our best option to take these HVIs out.
现在，准备发射一枚AGM-14“狱火”导弹
Now, prepare to launch a single AGM-114 Hellfire
到目标房屋
on the target house.
- 是，长官  - 这是一个友国城市
Yes, ma'am. This is a friendly city,
所以，附带损害必须降至最低
so collateral damage must be kept to a minimum.
- 长官…  - 什么？
Ma'am... Yes?
我有一个ROE问题
I have an ROE question.
我们的政府是否知道
Is my government aware that we are
我们正在把一个持美国护照的人作为目标？
targeting a person with a US passport?
是的，是的，中尉
Yes. Yes, it is, Lieutenant.
我在SPINS上，什么也没看到
I didn't see anything in the SPINS about that.
中尉，我们已经有了新的交战规则
Lieutenant, we have new rules of engagement.
你是受保护的
You are covered.
动作必须快，所以准备好投弹吧
This is going to happen fast, so be ready to shoot.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
正在检查三十四项清单
Running the dash 34 checklist.
卡莉，准备好了就呼叫我
Carrie, call when ready.
你以前有发射过狱火吗？
You ever shot a Hellfire?
没有
No.
其他弹药呢？
Or anything?
没有，我只当了一年天眼
No. I've only ever been the eye.
你呢？
You?
我也没有
Me, too.
伙计们，看来今天是你们的幸运日
Looks like it's your lucky day today, guys.
保持冷静，好吗？谨慎点
Just stay cool, okay? Be all right.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
卡莉，准备好了就呼叫
Carrie, call when ready.
倾斜范围二点二万英尺
Slant range 22,000 feet.
高冲击角
High-impact angle.
准备好目标简报
Stand by for targeting brief.
准备
Ready.
安吉拉，我同意我们有被视为是
Angela, I agree, we are at risk of being perceived
在从事击杀政策的风险
as embarking on a shoot-to-kill policy.
但既然所有的法律条件都充分
But since all the legal criteria are sound,
我确定，我们必须允许继续这项军事行动
I believe we must allow this military action to continue.
法律上我们也许是安全的
Legally we may be safe,
但政治上，我们这好比是在越雷池
but politically we're walking into a minefield.
尤其是里面还包含了一名美国公民
Especially with an American citizen involved.
首相，是否允许？
Do I have permission, Minister?
呃…
Um...
考虑到这个情况，这是任务转变
Given the situation, that it is a change of mission,
现在成了用导弹袭击英国目标
that it is now a missile attack on a British subject,
两名英国目标，和一名美国公民
two British subjects, and an American citizen,
而且是在一个友国
and in a friendly country,
我认为唯一合理的做法是
I think it is only right and proper
向外交部长上报
that I refer this up to the Foreign Secretary.
首相，刚才的争论你听见了，而他没听见
Minister, you've heard the arguments, he hasn't.
而且交战规则意味着
And the rules of engagement mean that
首相已经认可了它
the Prime Minister has already approved it.
- 不…  - 因此
No... Therefore,
外交部长无需提出意见
the Foreign Secretary's input should not be rendered...
不，重点是我之前没有参与
No, the point is that I have not been party
任何与首相的
to any previous discussion with the Prime Minister
关于此类事件的讨论
about matters such as this,
反之，外交部长是肯定参与了的
whereas the Foreign Secretary undoubtedly has.
所以，向他上报是我的义务
So, actually, it is my duty to refer to him.
那我怎么回复鲍威尔上校？
And what am I telling Colonel Powell?
让她等！
Tell her to wait!
我的苍天！
Oh, Christ Almighty!
新加坡，国际武器贸易展销会
谢谢
Thank you.
作为英国政府的成员
As a member of the British government,
我很自豪地向大家介绍综合战场解决方案
I am proud to introduce Integrated Battlefield Solutions,
一家英国公司带领了生产
a UK company leading the field in the production
自救，轻型的军事服装领域
of life-saving, lightweight military clothing.
在战场上保护我们的士兵
Protecting our soldiers in the field of battle
是我们政府对我们的军队
is at the core of my government's
恪守的核心
commitment to our armed forces.
“士兵安全第一” 就是我们为什么在…
"Soldier safety first" is why we 're in...
抱歉
Excuse me.
天呐，他要吐了！
Oh, God, he's gonna throw up!
我早跟他说，别吃大虾了
I told him not to eat the prawns.
抱歉
Excuse me.
很高兴向大家介绍IBS的常务董事
And so I'm very pleased to introduce you to IBS Managing Director.
奈杰尔·阿德勒先生
Mr. Nigel Adler.
非常感谢，外交部长
Thank you very much, Foreign Secretary.
今天我们要介绍坚固的防弹衣系统
Today we're introducing the Adamant Assault Body Armor System.
- 我们收到CDE了没？  - 是的，长官
Do we have that CDE yet? Yes, ma'am.
很好
Good.
如果我们以角落的这个房间为目标，也就是爆炸物的所在位置
If we target this corner room here, where the explosives are,
那个房间将发生百分百的死亡率
we would expect 100% mortality rate in that room
而其他房间的死亡率，则在百分之八十到百分之九十
and an 80 to 90% rate within the rest of the house.
集市是安全的
The market should be safe,
但街上的这片区域
but this area here in the street...
死亡率是百分之六十五到百分之七十五
A 65 to 75% rate.
那就是狱火的武力
That's just the Hellfire.
如果我们将爆炸背心计算在内
If we factor in the explosives in the vests,
那这片区域的损害范围将更大
we're looking at even more extensive damage way out to this area here.
但我无法精确计算那个范围
But I can't accurately estimate that yield.
但我们要包括那屋里
But we would be containing that payload in the vests
背心里的弹药，对吗？
within those walls, right?
附加损害远远达不到
Far less collateral damage
伤害集市里的人群
than them going off in a crowded shopping mall.
是的，没错
Yes. Of course.
对，谢谢
Yeah. Thank you.
显然，没有人在避免做出决定
Obvious to anyone not trying to avoid making a decision.
和马来西亚贸易部长的会议在四点半
The meeting with the Malaysian Trade Minister is now at 4:30.
你得替我去了
You'll have to do it for me.
但是，先生，我们来这的整个重点是…
But, sir, the whole point of us being here...
对，也许你可以吃片抗过敏药
Yeah, maybe if you take an Eezi Tum.
听着，我现在必须回酒店
Look. I need to go back to the hotel now.
杰克，这交通阻塞是怎么回事？
Jack, what's the holdup?
抱歉，先生，我已经在尽力联系他了
I'm sorry, sir, I'm trying to reach him.
首相，拖延决定
Minister, the consequences of delay
也许对大量市民们来说是致命的
may be fatal to scores of civilians.
上将，我很清楚这点
I'm well aware of that, General,
但得到他的认可，对我来说，是合理程序
but it is the proper procedure for me to seek his approval.
如果这些人现在分开乘坐汽车离开
If these men leave now, in separate vehicles...
那外面停了两辆车
There are two vehicles outside,
我们只有能力跟踪一辆
we have the ability to follow only one.
我们只有一个天眼
We have only one eye in the sky.
你在地面上的特工们应该可以拦截吧？
Surely you have agents on the ground who could intercept?
拦截城市街头的自杀炸弹袭击者？
Intercept a suicide bomber on a city street?
我们是想最大程度的减少附带损伤
We're trying to minimize collateral damage.
肖曼5-0，北2-0
Showman 5-0, North 2-0.
我发出攻击命令后，你必须
When I give the order to attack, you have to
让你的人立即离开
get your man out of there immediately.
我们大概三分钟就会到达
He'll have about three minutes.
明白
Understood.
我们一切正常，导弹状态稳定
We are greened up. Missile status is ready.
只要选择目标，编码，准备完毕
Left selected for single fire, coded and ready.
待命
Stand by.
你可以测试激光了
You're cleared to test the laser.
激光打开，状态良好
Laser on. Good laser.
快啊，长官
Oh, come on, sir.
我们需要许可，他们不会永远呆在那房子里
We need a go. They ain't gonna be in that house forever.
镇静点，好吗
Just keep it together, all right?
是
Yes, sir.
我们需要作出决定，部长
We need a decision, Minister.
现在
Right now.
谢谢，谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
外交部的电话
I have the Foreign Secretary.
嗯哼？
Mmm-hmm?
布莱恩来电话
It's Brian on your phone.
- 哪个布莱恩  - 伍德代尔
- Brian who? - Woodale.
他要什么？我现在没法跟他说话
What does he want? I can't talk to him now.
很紧急，他在眼镜蛇
It's urgent. He's at Cobra.
检查表对照完毕，安全检查已经完毕
The checklist is complete. Safety checklist complied with.
已捕获攻击低点
Desired point of impact is captured.
ROE还没回应，我们正在待命
ROE is pending. We're standing by for clearance.
先生们，没有美国国务院的许可
Gentlemen, I cannot authorize a missile attack on an American citizen
我不能授权攻击美国公民
without the approval of the US Secretary of State.
先生，国务卿在中国
Sir, the Secretary of State is in China.
那就找到他
Then track him down.
外交部，我是本森将军
Foreign Secretary, it's General Benson here.
恕我直言
With respect,
这件事已经经过了美国总统的解释
this has already been cleared at American Presidential level.
我们现在的状况在十分钟后可能导致…
We have a situation here which could result in massive loss of life
大规模人员伤亡
in the next 10 minutes.
那就用那十分钟争取到国务卿的许可
Then use those 10 minutes and get the Secretary's approval.
那就是我的决定，将军
That is my decision, General.
我去联系北京大使馆
I'll get onto the Embassy in Beijing.
我最好跟他谈谈，借过
I'd better speak to him. Excuse me.
凯特，把我的笔记本连上线
Kate. Get me linked in on my laptop. Sir?
- 是  - 这就去
Yes, sir. Got it.
噢
Oh!
好吧，太尴尬了，对不起
Okay, that was embarrassing. Sorry.
准备好了？等我一下
Ready? Just give me a second.
国务卿先生，乔丹·里卡多打来的电话
Mr. Secretary, I have Jordan Ricardo on the line.
谁？
Who?
北京大使馆的乔丹·里卡多
Jordan Ricardo, from our embassy here in Beijing.
非常紧急
It's urgent.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
先生，我们接到英国打来的电话，关于一个行动的
Sir, we've received a call from the British regarding an operation.
为什么要拿这种事情来浪费我的时间
Why the hell are you wasting my time referring this to me?
不，他的公民身份不能保护他
No, his citizenship does not protect him.
通过加入青年党已经宣布了
By joining Al-Shabab he has declared
他是美国的敌人
himself an enemy of the United States.
听我说
Listen to me.
告诉英国人，要是他们真的
Tell the British, if they really do have
在东非发现了第二、四和五号人物
two, four, and five on the East Africa list in their sights,
我们完全支持他们攻击
they have our full support to strike.
对，这三个都在总统的名单上
Yes, all three are on the President's list.
好，来吧，耶
Okay, let's go! Yeah!
我一定要赢你
I'm gonna get you, Jian.
国务卿许可了
The Secretary of State has given his permission.
可以开始了
You may proceed.
谢谢，部长
Thank you, Minister.
噢
Oh!
谢谢
Thank you.
夫人
Ma'am.
中尉，可以消灭目标
Lieutenant, you have clearance to prosecute the target.
马上动手
Do it now.
是，女士
Yes, ma'am.
准备发射地狱火导弹
Prepare to launch Hellfire.
我以为最糟糕的部分已经过去了
I think I'm through the worst of it.
出什么事了
What's happening?
国务卿同意了
The Secretary gave his permission.
他们在两万英尺高空有架掠食者
They have a Reaper at 20,000 feet
还在房间里装了微型监控
and a micro RPA inside the house.
武器准备完毕
Weapon is armed.
一切正常，激光状态良好
All green. Good laser.
DPI为房间中心
DPI is the center of the room.
收到，正校准目标
Copy. Crosshairs on it now.
待命
Stand by.
- 确认PAX状态  - 一切正常
- Confirm PAX status. - All good.
祝你好运
Good luck.
三
Three.
二
Two.
那是个孩子吗？放大
Is that a kid? Zoom in.
我给她时间走过去
I'll give her time to walk through.
夫人？
Ma'am?
你可以开火，中尉
You are cleared to engage, Lieutenant.
她停下了
She stopped.
中尉，我们只有这次机会，不要弄丢了
Lieutenant, we have this one opportunity. Let's not lose it.
夫人，她在卖饼
Ma'am, uh, she's selling bread.
天啊
Jesus.
那些人就要离开了，马上发射
Those men are about to disperse. Engage now.
夫人，我明白我们获得许可了
Ma'am, I understand we have clearance.
如果看到HVI移动我会发射
I will fire if I see the HVIs moving
或者等这女孩离开爆炸范围
or when this girl's out of the frag radius,
但我想给她个离开的机会
but I want to give her a chance to get out of the way.
中尉，你已经获得许可
Lieutenant, you have clearance.
这图像中包含的威胁比你想的要大
There is a lot more at stake than you see here in this image.
夫人，我需要将女孩包含在内后
Ma'am, I need you to run the collateral damage estimate
再进行一次附带损伤估算
again with this girl out front.
情况没有变化，中尉，你可以发射
The situation has not changed, Lieutenant. You are cleared to engage.
我们怎么办？
What do we do?
重复，可以发射
I repeat, you are cleared to engage.
鲍威尔上校，夫人
Colonel Powell, ma'am...
我是负责发射武器的驾驶员
I'm the pilot in command responsible for releasing the weapon.
我有权要求再次进行CDE
I have the right to ask for the CDE to be run again.
在那之前我不会发射武器
I will not release my weapon until that happens.
那就再做CDE
We will rerun CDE.
操
Fuck.
现在是否是“武器待命”
Do I understand we are now on "weapons hold"?
武器待命
Weapons hold.
- 中尉，重新做CDE  - 是，长官
- Sergeant, rerun CDE. - Yes, ma'am.
史蒂夫，你在干什么？
Steve, what the fuck are you doing?
你刚拿规定甩了一个上校一脸
You just threw the rule book at a colonel.
长官，我会管理好武器
Sir, I am safing up the weapon
直到你给我带有新CDE结果的许可
until you read me a new clearance with a new CDE.
干得好
Well done.
肖曼5-0，北部2-0
Showman 5-0, North 2-0,
能不能让你那里开甲壳虫的人
can you get your man with a beetle in there
去买下这女孩的饼，让她离开那
to buy this girl's bread, get her out of there?
见鬼
Shit!
操
Fuck!
能把视线转回房子上吗
Can you get me back to the house?
是，上校
Yes, Colonel.
卡莉，别管他，回到目标上
Carrie, forget him. Get back to the target.
卡莉
Carrie.
回到目标上
Back to the target.
天啊，她会再卖一次的
Jesus, she's gonna sell them again.
我们还能让谁去买饼？
Who else can we get to buy the bread?
别管饼了，中士
Forget the bread, Sergeant.
要是我们的人没把整个行动搞砸，就算运气好了
We'll be lucky if our man hasn't blown the whole operation.
哈罗德，在法律上我们怎么样
Harold, where are we legally?
- 加上小女孩？  - 对
With the girl? Yes.
- 有问题吗  - 呃
Are we in the clear? Uh...
我还是建议转交上级处理
Again, I would refer up.
不，不，我是问你
No. No. I'm asking you.
我们不能再拖延这次行动了
We cannot hold up this operation any longer.
我们需要采取所有合理的措施，来最小化附带损伤
We need to take all reasonable steps to minimize collateral damage.
如果我们买下她的饼那…
If we're buying her bread then...
我们不会
We're not.
我们不会买她的饼，那结束了
We're not buying her bread. That's over.
很多孩子的生命处在危险当中，而这只是一个女孩
Many children's lives are at risk. This is just one girl.
我们能不能发射？行还是不行？快点，做个决定
Are we clear to engage, yes or no? Come on, make a decision.
恕我直言，长官，这些决定不是我来做的
With respect, ma'am, I don't make those decisions.
我是来给你法律方面的建议
I'm here to advise you on the law!
法律不是来阻挠你
The law is not here to get in your way,
而是来保护你，保护你的目标的
it is here to protect you, and to protect your target.
别对我说教，哈罗德
Don't lecture me, Harold!
长官，必要以及相关的法律问题
Ma'am, the legal questions of necessity
都已经解决了
and proportionality are almost certainly met.
但为了保护你
But for the protection of you,
以及保护那个女孩
and for the protection of that girl,
我建议把问题上交给司法部长
I would refer up to the Attorney General.
本森
Benson.
弗兰克，我能跟司法部长说话吗
Frank, may I speak to the Attorney General?
接通司法部长
Connect us to Colonel Powell.
乔治
George.
她想跟你说话
She wants to talk to you.
说吧，凯瑟琳
Go ahead, Katherine.
长官，我们的律师说这女孩的存在
Sir, our lawyer says the girl's presence
不会改变我们行动的合法性
has not necessarily altered the legitimacy of our operation.
但他需要确认
But he does need that confirmed.
我们有没有估计她可能发生什么？
Do we have an assessment of what might happen to her?
目标估算她有百分之六十五到百分之七十五的可能性
The targeteer assesses a 65 to 75% chance
遭遇致命伤害
of fatal injury should we proceed.
但她同样关乎八十名…
But he has also assessed a projected loss of life
男女老沙的安危
of up to 80 men, women and children
如果爆炸背心在城市区域引爆
if the vests are detonated in an urban area.
虽然这只是猜测
Now that's a guess, of course,
但我们应该假设他们打算攻击人口密集区域
but we should assume they intend to target a crowded location.
百分之六十五的几率
A 65% assessment
要求我们尽一切可能
requires us to do whatever we can
让她能够离开现场
to enable her to be removed from the scene.
我们在有限的时间里
We have done what we can for her
已经进了一切所能
in the time available to us.
如果我们继续等，他们离开
If we wait and they leave,
我们就无法再控制情况了
we will no longer have control of the situation.
我们必须现在攻击
We must strike now.
没有法律解释这样的情况
There is no law covering a situation quite like this.
趁街上没人发射导弹
It's one thing to release a missile whilst the street is clear
并希望没人会上那条街是一回事
in the hope that it will remain so.
但知道这个女孩最严重的后果
It's quite another thing knowing that
就是遭遇致命损伤
this girl will,
或是起码受重伤
at worst, be fatally injured
则是另一回事
and, at best, severely injured.
很抱歉，我不同意你在诺斯伍德的律师的分析
So, I'm sorry, I disagree with the assessment of your lawyer at Northwood.
同意
Agreed.
希望“她是个贴心的小女孩”这评价没有包含你的判断
I hope the fact that she's a sweet little girl is not clouding your judgment.
如果这些人离开
Dozens of other little girls' lives
几十个其他小女孩的生命就会有危险
are at stake if these men leave.
对不起，但白宫的吉丽安·古德曼小姐
I'm sorry, but we have a Miss Jillian Goldman from the White House
要求接入通话
asking to be patched in.
- 谁？  - 吉丽安·古德曼
Who? Jillian Goldman.
她是美国国家安全委员会的高级法律顾问
She's a Senior Legal Adviser at the US National Security Council.
国务卿把情况向她简要介绍了
She's been briefed by the Secretary of State.
接过来
Put her through.
下午好，谢谢你们允许我评论
Good afternoon and thank you for allowing me to comment.
是的，谢谢你加入我们
Yeah, thanks for joining us.
你们也知道作为军队成员
As the military members of your committee know,
我们有个与附带损失评估相关的评分系统
we have a point system that takes into account collateral damage
来推断一个行动究竟是否合法
to deduce what is and what is not a legal strike.
我直接跟你说吧
And let me tell you categorically
这新情况的存在
that the existence of this new circumstance
不会让我们超出合法军事行动的范畴
does not push us beyond a legitimate military action.
我们的这一行动远远称不上“有争议”
We are way off what we would consider a dispute in this matter.
古德曼小姐，我们对附带损伤这个问题
Miss Goldman, we have a somewhat different approach
有不同的看法
to the question of collateral damage.
先生，你必须现在行动，你有两个人
Sir, you must act now. You have two men
即将开始自杀式任务
about to embark on a suicide mission.
你已经监控了总统东非清除名单上的
You have number two, four, and five
第二、四和五号人物
on the President's East Africa kill list in your sights,
你要因为一个附带损失
and you are putting the whole mission at risk
就让整个任务遇到危机？
because of one collateral damage issue?
我意识到这次任务是你发起的
I realize that this mission is your call,
如果你让这些人去
but there would be some mighty angry people
把一个购物中心炸上天，那你将面对…
here at the White House and at the Pentagon, and out there in the world
来自白宫，五角大楼
if you allow these people to leave
以及世界各地的人民的愤怒
and blow a shopping mall to kingdom come.
对不起，外交部长想加入
I'm sorry. We have the Foreign Secretary wanting to join.
好的，感谢你的意见，古德曼小姐
Right. We appreciate your thoughts, Miss Goldman.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你
大家下午好，请原谅我这身衣服
Good afternoon, everybody. Excuse my appearance.
这边是晚上，我还有点水土不服
It's night here, and I have a bout of food poisoning.
抱歉把你从病床上拉起来
Sorry to drag you from your sick bed.
没错
That's quite all right.
乔治，我理解的是对的吗
George, do I understand this correctly?
关于等待那女孩
There's a legal argument for waiting
给她个机会把饼卖完，还存在法律上的争论？
and giving this girl a chance to sell her bread?
是的
Yes, there is.
但相反的，这不意味着
But, conversely, it does not mean
现在发射武器
that there is not also a legal argument
就不会带来法律问题
for releasing the weapon now.
请原谅，我不知道这对我有什么帮助
Forgive me, I'm not sure that helps me.
外交部长，现在采取军事行动是必须的
Foreign Secretary, there is a military necessity for acting now.
在我们看来，他们随时会离开那幢房子
In our view, they'll be making a move from that house at any moment.
先生们，有什么任务是合法的推荐给我的？
Gentlemen, what action is being legally recommended to me?
詹姆斯，法律争论是我们可以等
James, the legal argument is that we could wait,
但不需要等的
but we need not wait.
军事行动方面的争议则是不能等
And the military argument is that we should not wait.
- 对吗  - 没错
Right? Exactly.
是我建议不应该拖延
It's my recommendation that we should not delay
执行这次任务
in proceeding with this mission.
如果现在不行动，就会冒着
If we don't act now, we risk losing
失去八十条人命的风险
the lives of up to 80 people.
这些死亡你只能估算
You can only assume those deaths.
能确定的是，如果我们现在行动
What is certain is that if we do act now,
这一个女孩会很惨
this one girl will suffer.
你会救她，然后搭上另外八十条性命？
And you would save her and risk killing 80 others?
对，我会救她然后冒那个险
Yes, I would save her and take that risk.
那就是我会做的
That is what I would do.
安吉拉，到时候电视报道
Angela, is it you or me who will be invited onto the Today program
商场炸弹袭击中八十人丧生
to explain why we knew of the attack
而我们却没有阻止
on a shopping center that killed 80 people,
他们会请的人是你还是我？
but chose to do nothing to stop it?
是你，詹姆斯
You, James.
但说实话，从政治上说，我更愿意指出
But frankly, politically, I'd rather point to Al-Shabab
青年党才是杀死八十人的凶手
as murderers of 80 people shopping
而不是为我们的军队发起的
than have to defend a drone attack
害死一名无辜女孩的无人机攻击辩护
by our forces that kills an innocent child.
詹姆斯，安吉拉这个观点很明确
James, Angela makes a compelling point.
如果青年党杀死八十个人，我们就能赢得道义
If Al-Shabab kill 80 people, we win the propaganda war.
如果我们杀一个孩子，他们就赢
If we kill one child, they do.
那我们什么都不做？
So, we don't do it?
她有个客人
She's got a customer.
我建议你盯着另一个屏幕
I suggest you keep your eyes on the other screen.
恕我直言，外交部长
With respect, Foreign Secretary,
另外八十条人命也包括无辜的孩子
are the lives of 80 people, including innocent children,
为了赢得道义真的需要付出这么大的代价吗
really worth the price of winning the propaganda war?
将军，如果我们攻击，我们攻击的视频会泄露吗
General, if we go ahead, might footage of our attack be leaked?
长官，来自掠食者的视频是绝对安全的
Sir, the footage from the Reaper is completely secure.
将军，如果我们不再等一会
General, I would feel uncomfortable
我会觉得不安的
if we did not at least wait a little longer.
如果我们攻击，视频泄露这女孩被杀
If we go ahead and footage is leaked and this girl is killed,
我认为国内民众会非常反感
then, I think, the country would be most disturbed.
外交部长，我们的任务就是
Foreign Secretary, it is our task
做出正确的军事决定
to make the right military decision.
我们不能参与到将来视频网站上
We cannot engage in an argument
可能发生的争论之中
about possible future postings on YouTube.
恕我直言，将军，那些网站上的视频连革命都能煽动
With respect, General, revolutions are fueled by postings on YouTube.
我认为既然后果会这么严重
I think the consequences are such
我们需要获得首相的许可
that we need clearance from the PM.
詹姆斯，你有作出决定的权力
James! You have the authority to make a decision!
不，我告诉你，你得把问题教给他
No, I'm telling you. You need to take it to him.
先生，首相今天下午要在斯特拉斯堡发表演讲
Sir, the PM is giving a speech in Strasbourg this afternoon,
可能不太好打断
and may not be easily interrupted.
这就交给你解决了，杰克
I'll leave you to sort that one out, Jack.
是，先生
Yes, sir.
我去联系他
I'll track him down.
喂
Yes?
长官，怎么了
Ma'am, what's happening?
你在待命中，中尉
You're on standby, Lieutenant.
是
Yes, ma'am.
还在踢皮球
Still on the chain.
还剩两块面饼
Two loaves left.
我们得等等
We gotta wait now.
快啊
Come on.
长官，电池没电了
Ma'am, the battery died.
我们的人倒下了，我们没法替换
Our man is down. We can't replace it.
天啊
Christ.
- 出什么事了  - 电池
What happened? Battery.
噢，天啊
Oh, for God's sake!
现在我们不知道他们在干什么了
Now we have no idea what they're doing.
我也许有个办法
I might have a solution.
如果我的瞄准手能够计算出
If my targeteer can calculate us
女孩遭遇附带损伤的几率在百分之五十以下
coming in under 50% for collateral damage on the girl,
你那边能够获得许可吗
do you think you can get approval at your end?
是的
Yes, I do.
谢谢
Thanks.
电池
Battery.
赛德中士
Sergeant Saddiq,
我们想把这边这条街的附带损伤
we're looking to present the collateral damage
算出致命度在百分之四十到百分之五十之间
in the street, in this area right here, as 45 to 50% fatality.
你认为那可能吗
Do you think that's possible?
我算出来的是六十五到七十五
I've calculated a 65 to 75.
是的，当然
Yes, yes. Sure, sure,
但你知道，如果我们把导弹瞄准这里和这里
but, you know, if we put the payload here, or here,
或者也许这里
or maybe here,
那就能确保目标致命
well, then we could guarantee the target fatality,
但能降低损伤
but we could reduce the collateral.
或者也许能让导弹瞄准这里
Or maybe we could target the missile right here, look.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
你能不能…
Will you just...
尽你一切所能救这女孩的命
You just do whatever you can to save this girl's life.
我就交给你了
I'll leave it with you.
是
Yes, ma'am.
如果我们要向内罗毕的人宣布
If we have to announce to the people of Nairobi
我们知道一切但没有行动…
that we knew everything but did nothing...
我们不需要宣布我们知道任何事，将军
We do not have to announce that we knew anything, General.
首相要我们尽可能减小伤亡
The PM asks that we do what we can to minimize casualties.
- 该死的懦夫  - 你以为我们在干什么
Bloody coward! What do you think we're doing?
你怎么理解这话，乔治
How do you interpret that, George?
部长，我们不能让受命于政府的委员会
Minister, we cannot have military decisions
来做出军事方面的决定
dictated by government committees.
更不能在军事行动的每个阶段都停下来
Nor can we put on hold a military operation at every stage
等待法律许可
for legal clarification.
你让我们什么时候去打仗，我们就打
You tell us when to go to war, we conduct the war,
剩下的你来处理
you deal with the aftermath.
要那么简单就好了
If only it were that simple.
抱歉又要催你了，中士，但我们没多少时间
Sorry to rush you, Sergeant, but we don't have much time.
是
Yes, ma'am.
长官
Ma'am.
- 把攻击点调到这里  - 嗯哼
Adjusting the point of impact to here... Mmm-hmm.
致命几率就只有百分之四十五到百分之六十五
There is a 45 to 65% possibility of fatality.
- 百分之六十五  - 对
65%? Yes.
不，我需要把计算结果降到百分之五十以下
No, I need that calculation to be below 50%.
也许能评估一下
Perhaps there could be an assessment
目标点在这里的损伤
of the impact of the damage right here.
计算结果已经是我认为最低的了
That calculation is already at the lowest limit of what I believe is possible.
要是让导弹击中这里呢
What if you put the missile there?
我还是必须
I would still have to make that
把可能上限定为百分之六十五
a 65% possibility on the upper limit.
中士，我们要让行动成功
Sergeant, we need to make this work.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我们已经锁定了目标
We are locked into this kill chain.
我们必须作出决定，有…
- We have to make a decision. - There are...
有很多条人命在危险中
There are many lives at risk.
女士
Ma'am.
我认为
I think...
我认为如果我
I think if I
把这里作为攻击点
make this the point of impact, then...
在那里可以预测出百分之四十五的致命可能性
There I could predict a 45% possibility of fatality.
- 那是有可能的  - 百分之四十五？
That might be possible. 45%?
- 有可能  - 好的，太好了
Possibly. Good man. Good man.
我告诉眼镜蛇
I'll put that to Cobra.
长官
Ma'am.
这只是个估计
It's just an estimate.
对，当然，我明白
Yes, of course. Of course, I understand.
在这种情况下任何计算都只可能是估计
In these circumstances, any calculation can only be a speculation.
别担心
Don't worry.
这不会让你负担任何责任
This puts you beyond any culpability.
谢谢，谢谢，中士
Thank you. Thank you, Sergeant.
谢谢，长官
Thanks, ma'am.
长官，我已经收到瞄准手的评估
Sir, I have a revised assessment from the targeteer.
如果你看图表
If you would look at the diagram.
把导弹瞄准这里
By targeting the missile here,
在女孩所处的这个区域
there is an estimated 45% chance of fatality
只有百分之四十五的致命可能
in this area here, where the girl is positioned.
我们已经做了一切
We have now done everything in our power
来给那女孩一线生机
to give this girl a chance to survive.
谢谢，上校
Thank you, Colonel.
部长
Minister.
我们有权消灭目标了吗
Do we have authority to prosecute the target?
- 百分之四十五？  - 百分之四十五
45%? 45%.
是的
Yes.
你可以攻击
You may proceed.
长官
Ma'am.
瓦特斯中尉，CDE已经重新进行
Lieutenant Watts, we have rerun the CDE.
你已被授权消灭目标
You are authorized to prosecute the target.
我的计算员正发送调整过的DPI
My targeteer is sending through the adjusted DPI.
现在攻击，明白了吗
Engage now. Am I clear?
是，上校
Yes, Colonel.
可以开火
Cleared to engage.
运行-34检查表
Running the dash 34 checklist.
卡莉，准备好了告诉我
Carrie, call when ready.
准备好了
Ready.
武器系统启动
Weapon systems on.
激光感应器？
Laser sensor?
确认
Check.
- 坐标系？  - 确认
Gimbal? Released.
倾斜范围确定
Slant range set.
系统电量正常
System power, nominal.
指定输出，正常
Designated power, nominal.
导弹？
Missile?
已输入
Coded.
平均海拔设定为标准
Mean altitude set to standard.
GPS信号
GPS signal...
确认
Check.
一号卫星锁定？
Satellite 1 lock?
确认
Check.
二号卫星锁定？
Satellite 2 lock?
确认
Check.
武器
Arm weapon.
确认
Check.
武器状态
Weapon status.
确认
Check.
三，二
Three, two,
一
one.
步枪，步枪，步枪，武器发射
Rifle, rifle, rifle. Weapon away.
飞行时间五十秒
Time of flight, 50 seconds.
有个男孩
There's a boy!
见鬼
Oh, shit!
等等，他在买…他在买面包
Wait, he's buy... He's buying the bread.
四十秒
Forty seconds.
快点，快点，快点
Come on, come on, come on.
走啊
Go!
她在动
She's moving.
放大，我们需要知道是否命中目标
Zoom in. We need to know that we've hit our targets.
是，上校
Yes, Colonel.
史蒂夫，确认尸体
Steve, identify the bodies.
放大
Zoom in.
尸体辨认可能是拉希德·哈穆德
Body identified as probably Rasheed Hamud.
尸体未知，可能是阿卜杜拉·阿尔·哈迪
Body unknown, but likely Abdullah Al-Hady.
我们需要再次攻击
We need to re-engage.
上校
Colonel!
再次攻击
We're going again.
她在名单上
She's on the list.
中尉
Lieutenant.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
瞄准活动的人
Target the moving body.
是，长官
Yes, ma'am.
攻击目标
Engaging target.
系统依然正常，导弹准备
System is still green. Ready on the red missile.
目标捕获
Target is captured.
三，二
Three, two,
一
one.
步枪，步枪，步枪，武器发射
Rifle, rifle, rifle. Weapon away.
飞行时间，五十秒
Time of flight, 50 seconds.
阿丽亚
Alia.
史蒂夫，你需要让我们靠近观察丹佛的尸体
Steve, you need to get us close in on the remains of Danford.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
卡莉，我们需要辨认尸体
Carrie, we need to go identify the body.
根据我看到的视频
Based on the footage I'm seeing,
尸体确认为苏珊·海伦·丹佛
body confirmed as Susan Helen Danford.
本森
Benson.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
干得好，凯瑟琳
Well done, Katherine.
谢谢，长官
Thank you, sir.
对不起，赛德，我看不到还有别的选择
I'm sorry, Sadd, I couldn't see any other option.
是的，女士，我明白
Yes, ma'am, I understand that.
现在把你报告中的CDE结果写成百分之四十五
Now, you will file your report as a 45% CDE.
明白吗
Understood?
赛德？
Sadd?
百分之四十五
45%.
是，上校
Yes, Colonel.
在我看来
In my opinion,
那太丢人了
that was disgraceful.
这一切都是为了保住你的位置
And all done from the safety of your chair.
我亲自参与了五起
I have attended the immediate aftermath
自杀式袭击的善后工作
of five suicide bombings
就在现场，跟尸体在一起
on the ground, with the bodies.
你今天喝着咖啡吃着饼干看到的事
What you witnessed today with your coffee and biscuits
是很难看
is terrible.
但这些人可能做出的事会更难看
What these men would've done would've been even more terrible.
永远不要跟士兵说
Never tell a soldier
他不懂战争的代价
that he does not know the cost of war.
长官
Sir.
噢
Oh...
谢谢，上尉
Thank you, Captain.
做得很好，你们俩都是
You did well. Both of you.
谢谢，长官
Thank you, sir.
你们应该回家去，休息一下
You should go home. Get some rest.
我需要你们俩在十二点回到这里
I need you both back here in 12 hours.
好吗
All right?